[haunting music playing]
[promo intro playing]
[announcer]
Killer Whales or Orcas
are the ocean's top predators,
growing up to 32 feet and
weighing up to 5 tons.
Social and highly intelligent,
they hunt everything from fish
to whales
and have highly
evolved problem-solving skills.
At World of Orca, Ceto has been
our superstar for 20 years,
engaging with humans
and living a stress-free life.
Your ticket supports
orca conservation
and Ceto's well-being.
It's Ceto's world!
[unsettling music playing]
[announcer]
Killer Whales or Orcas
are the ocean's top predators ,
growing up to 32 feet...
-All right, that's me done.
-You go.
If I stay here much longer,
I'm going to go insane.
-I'll lock up.
-Chelsea, you've done
nights all week.
-She's just not the same
since they lost the calf.
-What, Poseidon?
-Yeah.
-They say he died.
-That's what they always say.
[whispers] She knows.
You can tell.
It's like... [exhales]
...it's like...
she's waiting.
-Okay, well,
don't stay out too late.
-Okay.
-Bye.
[Chelsea] Ceto!
Come on, baby.
Ceto!
Where are you, baby?
-[clicks tongue]
-[unsettling music playing]
Come on, baby.
[unsettling music continues]
Ceto.
Come here, baby.
Where are you?
[unsettling music continues]
[Ceto clicks]
[tense music]
[breathing heavily]
[screams]
[dramatic music playing]
[haunting atmospheric music
playing]
[atmospheric cello music
[cello music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[cello music continues
playing over headphones]
-[Chad] Working hard or...
-[Maddie gasps]
...or hardly working?
Oh my God.
Oh, Chad, you scared
the crap out of me. [laughs]
-I'm sorry.
-[Maddie laughs]
How did you even get in here?
Uh, well, a magician
never tells, you know that.
You left the back door unlocked,
Maddie, you gotta lock the door.
I know, I do that every time.
[Chad]
Anyone could walk in here.
Steal you, I don't know.
Was Trish still
at the grad party?
Oh, yeah. Trish was there.
She, uh, graced us part-timers
with her PhD presence.
She was busy, though.
Some biotech tutorial.
They were six
tequila shots deep.
That's a lot. She's tiny.
She's small, but mighty.
-[laughs]
-[tender music playing]
-She wasn't mad that I...
took the last-minute shift
here instead?
No. No, I, uh...
I covered for you.
Said you're at home
practicing your cello.
Thanks.
You practice your cello, right?
I should be practicing.
[thunder rumbling]
-[cellphone trilling]
-[engine idles]
[Chad] I ahh...
I got you a little something
for our graduation.
-Oh my God.
-Uh, it's...
No, you didn't have to do that.
I technically
graduate next week.
I have my final performance
and stuff still.
It's, uh...
I don't know, it's kind of
a good luck charm.
[tender string music playing]
Uh, not that you need it.
I mean, you're final piece
is gonna kill it. [chuckles]
I didn't know cello or orca
or...
If you don't like it,
uh, we can--
No, no. I love it. [laughs]
[dramatic music playing]
[tender music resumes]
Something to, uh,
remember me by.
-Oh, come on.
-Once some hot-shot orchestra
whisks you away
around the world.
And leave this all behind?
Never.
[ominous music playing]
-[man] Oh, that's cute.
-[gasps, pants]
Hey, what's with the gun?
-[man] Phones on the counter.
-[Chad] Hey.
-Please.
-Sure, sure, sure.
Please don't hurt him,
-please don't hurt him.
Hey, we can talk about this man.
-We don't need to--
-You sit!
-Move. You, open cash register.
-[pants]
Let's go.
[Chad] It's okay.
[Maddie] Please, please,
-don't hurt anybody.
-Fill it!
[dramatic music continues]
[man] Let's go.
-[man] Come on.
-Here, here, here.
Hey, is that real?
Hey, don't even think about it.
-Chad!
-Shut up!
-[gun cocks]
-Give it.
-[man] Ain't got all day!
-I'm sorry. I'm trying.
Here, here, here.
-[gunshot]
-[Maddie screams]
[breathes heavily]
-[Chad groans]
-[man groans] Fuck!
-[Maddie] Chad!
-[Chad groans]
-[Chad grunts]
-[man grunts]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-[man grunts]
-[Chad groans]
-[Maddie] Oh my God, Chad!
-[gun cocks]
-Chad! [grunts]
-[grunts]
[gunshot fires]
[all noise fades]
[Maddie breathes heavily]
[high pitched ringing]
-[screams]
-[gun cocks]
-[Maddie pants]
-[gunshot fires]
-[man screams, groans]
[grunting, groaning]
[grunting]
[Chad] Okay. Stay, stay here.
-[Chad pants] Hey!
-[car door closes]
[engine starts]
[tender music playing]
-[Chad pants]
-[footsteps approaching]
[tender music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
-[high pitched tone]
-[Maddie sobbing]
-[engine revving distantly]
-[high pitched tone crescendos]
[soft music playing]
[hearing aid beeps]
[cellphone chimes]
[beeping]
[door knocks]
Thanks for answering, bitch.
-[Maddie laughs]
-[laughs]
[Maddie] Hi. [laughs]
[exclaims]
I can't believe you're here.
Yeah, it's, uh,
it's been a year.
Wow, how... how are you?
Well, you know,
if you'd answer your phone,
Maddie, you would know that.
-Hmm.
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
-Yeah.
-I've just been a little busy.
I know.
-It's good to see you.
-I miss you.
-I miss you, too.
It's so good to see your face,
but I am running out the door.
I'm late for work.
[Trish] Okay,
well, um, how do you...
feel about calling in sick for,
like, I don't know, seven days?
Why?
Because it's booked,
and it's paid for,
and we've only been talking
about this trip for, like, ever.
And it's gonna be fun,
and you don't look
nearly excited enough
about an adventure.
What are those?
Uh, hearing aid batteries.
Great. Uh, well, I'm not taking
no for an answer,
so are you packing or am I?
Okay, then.
I'll take this.
Bet I can find your passport.
[sighs] Jesus, is this
your grandmother's?
Look, Trish, um, things have
-just kind of changed for me.
-Oh God!
Since we've been talking
about this trip forever and--
Ah.
Told ya.
It's gonna be fun, Maddie.
You heard of that word?
It's gonna be hot and humid.
-[somber music playing]
-[Trish distantly] Cute.
You'll need a bikini.
Do you own a bikini?
[thunder rumbling]
[Maddie screams]
[Trish] Hello?
Maddie?
[somber music fades]
[Trish] Maddie.
Hey...
Hey, we're fighters...
right?
We always have been.
What other choice do we have?
It that an inspirational quote
from one of your reels.
So you do watch my posts.
[both laugh]
-You know it.
-[sniffles]
Hey, isn't it that... your
cello?
It is dusty, and the end pin...
it's broken.
Yeah.
I guess I just really
haven't been playing music
so much these days.
Okay, well, we better fix that.
[Maddie chuckles]
Hmm?
[sighs]
Okay.
Well, why don't you go make
yourself useful and...
like, drink the rest of my milk
or throw away
a take-out box or something.
["Set Me Free' playing]
Is that a yes?
-Yes.
-Yes! [chuckles]
-[song fades to background]
-[Trish] Thank you.
-[Maddie] Thanks.
[Trish] Toast time.
-You still remember this?
-Oh, it's been so long.
May your beer always be cold.
-Boys be hot.
-[Trish] Mm-hmm.
Come hell or high water.
It's you and me.
-No matter what!
-[Maddie] No matter what!
-Bitch, you remembered it.
-Hmm.
-[Trish] A whole decade later.
-And it still holds up.
It does still hold up. Yeah.
-Cheese.
-[camera shutter clicking]
-You're so pretty.
No, no, no, please,
please don't post it.
I'll be fired.
I'm serious. Please.
-Oops.
-Trish!
-I'm kidding. [laughs]
-Oh my God.
But we should get you fired.
Because, you know,
socials is a gold mine.
I'm never going to be
a poor girl ever again.
That's for sure.
Is that thing waterproof?
[chuckles] What do you think?
-I hope so.
-[Trish laughs]
Thank you.
-[sighs]
-[Maddie] Trish, not that
I'm not grateful
that you brought me here,
because I'm really,
really grateful. [laughs]
But why are you spending
your hard-earned money on this?
Why not?
Hmm?
Thanks.
-["We Stay Up" playing]
-To the perfect escape?
-[laughs] To the perfect escape.
-[Trish chuckles] Yeah.
-[Maddie] I'm going to do it!
-[woman] Hello!
-[girls laughing]
-[woman] Oh, hello.
-You scared us.
What about a flower
may help you feel better?
-Oh, that's so sweet.
-It's so beautiful for you.
-Thanks.
-[woman] It's good for you.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you. Oh, too much.
Here, you take it.
No, no, no, no, no. Keep it.
-Very kind.
-[Trish] But...
-do you think we could have...
-[woman] Very kind.
...the whales instead?
-[woman] Of course.
-Mummy whale
and, uh, baby whale.
-Yes, you can.
-Thank you so much.
Why?
Maybe it's a clue.
-A clue?
-[Trish] Mm-hmm.
[chuckles] To what?
The subject of your final piece.
-Yes.
-You and, uh, Chad's
favorite whale.
What was her name?
Ceto.
Maybe...
we came all the way here so that
you could, uh,
meet an old friend.
Trish.
What?
It's all you and Chad
ever talked about.
-You're joking.
-What do you mean? What's wrong?
Maddie.
[somber music playing]
Um, you can have
the mummy whale.
-[woman] Thank you.
-I'm going to deal
with my grumpy friend. Hey!
[exhales heavily]
[somber music continues]
[Trish] Hey!
I thought you would love this.
No, Trish.
-Why?
-[Maddie] Trish, I love you,
but I'm not paying to endorse
to see Ceto in captivity.
And her baby died two years ago
in that awful tank of pneumonia
or so they said.
It was obviously a lot.
But we came... [chuckles]
...all the way out here
from the other side
of the world,
to see Ceto in person.
Like you and Chad,
never could before.
Yes, because they were
in the wild.
Which is where
they're meant to be,
not confined to a fish tank.
Okay. You know what? I...
I totally misread the situation.
You're... you're right.
We... we can do something else.
Anything else. Okay just.
Just enjoy our holiday.
Can we please...
-[soft music playing]
-Okay.
Okay, fine.
-What do you want to do?
-[Trish] Yes!
Uh, two things to do.
We start with the alcohol.
And then,
we'll see where we land.
[Trish] So,
paddle-boarding lessons?
-What do you think? Yeah.
-[Josh] Paddle boarding lessons?
[Josh] It's easy,
you know, you'll figure it out.
-[Trish] Yeah, but you know...
-[Maddie] Here you go.
[Trish] Maddie!
-Hey.
-[Trish] This is Josh.
I'm trying to get him to give us
some paddle boarding lessons
'cause staying upright
is not really my forte, so...
[Maddie clears throat]
[Josh laughs]
Hey, uh, that place is a dump.
And I prefer
to see them out there.
-Where they belong.
-Exactly.
Out in the wild.
Where they're meant to be,
not confined to some fish tank.
Exactly. And that whale there?
Sad life.
-[Trish] So sad.
-You know, 20 years alone
in that tank.
-[Trish] Hmm. I know.
-And then she gets injured.
Can't do any of the...
the little show tricks.
-[Trish] Yeah, yeah.
-So they breed her.
-And then her baby dies.
-[Trish] Poseidon.
-"Or dies." Yeah.
-[Trish] Yeah.
[Josh] See, I think
they stole the baby.
And that's how Ceto got that
nasty scar across her face.
That's crazy.
I think the exact same thing.
Mm-hmm. Greedy arseholes
profiting her from pain.
Ah, says he,
displaying the brochure.
[Josh] Fair point. Here, look.
[Trish] Oh!
Wow, way to stick it to the man.
Oh, you want to
stick it to the man, huh?
-Sure.
-[Josh] Great.
We'll just kick back.
Wait for nightfall to come.
And then we go
show them what's up.
What do you think?
-I love that idea.
-I don't.
Great.
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughing]
[upbeat music continues]
[exclaiming]
[upbeat music ends]
-[Maddie laughing]
-[Trish laughing]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay. So, maybe, maybe
the booze and the pills
weren't the best idea.
[Trish laughs]
Give it back.
Are we doing this?
Hey, you are not
financially endorsing this.
-I'm not.
-[Trish] You're not.
You're just coming to say hi.
-Just say hi.
-It's going to be fun.
-It's going to be so much fun.
-Okay, I'll say hi.
-[Trish giggling]
[unsettling music playing]
[Trish] Oh.
-[Josh] Shh.
-[Trish laughs]
[Josh]
Go, go, go, go. [chuckles]
[unsettling music continues]
-[Trish laughing]
-[Josh] No, this way.
[Josh whispers]
You have to be quiet.
[Maddie] Wait up guys!
[Trish giggling] Put me down.
-[Josh] Woah, woah, woah.
-[Maddie] Oh, oh my God!
[Maddie] Hold on.
[unsettling music continues]
[Trish] Let's go!
[Trish] Okay.
Okay, come on, come on.
I don't know guys.
What if seeing her in person
is worse than--
She's not going to fit
in your suitcase.
At least you get
to have a moment with her.
Go see the whale.
Okay. Go. See the whale.
[button clicks]
[unsettling music continues]
-[electricity zapping]
-[Ceto calling]
[unsettling music fades]
[rumbling]
[hearing aid screeches]
[dramatic music playing]
[Ceto calls]
-[dramatic music continues]
-[Ceto calling]
[dramatic music continues]
[chuckles]
Hi.
[Ceto calling]
What have they done to you?
[music becomes somber]
I'm so sorry, Ceto.
I'm sorry
you're trapped in there.
[water splashes]
Trish!
Josh!
[Josh] Busy!
- He's fine, leave him alone.
[gasps]
[screams]
[pants]
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh my God!
-[Trish laughing]
-[Josh laughing]
You guys, guys. We have to go.
We have to go now.
-Hey!
-Maddie!
I... I saw, there was...
there was a body in the tank.
-Hey! What are you doing here?
-Oh! Go, go, go, go.
-Go!
-[Security] Hey!
-[exclaims]
-[Trish] Go, go, go!
-[Josh grunts] Let's go!
-Hurry, hurry. Go, go, go, go.
-[Guard] Stop!
-[Josh] Go, go, go!
-[Guarfd] Wait!
-[Maddie grunts]
-[grunting]
-[Guard] You, stop! Wait.
-[grunts]
-[suspenseful music fades]
Come in.
-[man] What?
-The cleaner.
The cleaner.
-In Ceto's tank.
- Again?!
-Yeah.
- Get rid of that damn fish!
-[waves crashing]
-[unsettling music playing]
-[Trish laughing]
-[Josh laughing]
-Shh.
-[seagulls mewing]
Good morning.
-Hi. Hi!
-Hi.
Hi.
We have...
a surprise for you.
Thanks. But, I've had
enough surprises for one trip.
Trish, I'm good.
No, no, no, no.
Please, trust me. You're...
you're going to love it.
I promise.
-["Follow My Shadow" playing]
-[jet ski engine revving]
[Trish exclaims]
[exclaims]
[song fades]
-[life jackets zipping]
-[Josh grunts]
-[Josh] Thank you.
-[Maddie] Thanks.
Trish. Trish?
[mystical music playing]
This is amazing.
What's it called?
[sighs] Well, I could tell you.
But then I have to kill you.
[Maddie] I don't understand.
How come nobody's here but us?
[Josh] Apparently
a bunch of stuff happened,
a couple years ago.
And no one ever
really came back since.
The locals say it's cursed.
But I say
it's a great hangover cure.
-I hope so.
-[scoffs]
Is that thing glued to her hand?
Yep.
Along with 850,000 followers.
Is it what she does
for a living?
[Trish]
Well, till I finish my thesis
on the use
of immune modification
through gene editing
to combat stem cell damage.
Yeah.
-Right. Well, okay.
-Yeah.
[chuckles] Okay, well, I didn't
understand a lot of those words.
What I do know is
I think you've had a little
-too much screen time today.
-[Trish] Excuse me! Excuse me.
Give me back my phone.
[grunts]
[Josh] Relax.
It'll be safe. It'll be
right here in the jet ski.
[sighs]
You've bring your phone, right?
-Yes, I have my phone.
-[whispers] Thank God.
My state-of-the-art
-waterproof wrapping.
-Oh, Maddie.
You were a dad in your
past life, you know that?
Thanks, I think.
All right, you two.
Tide's coming up
so we're gonna to get
this jet ski over the sand
and then you and I are going
to go for the ride of your life.
And...
I think I have something
a little more your speed.
-["Get Ready For" playing]
-[jet ski engine revving]
[exclaims]
-[exclaims]
-Hey!
[exclaims]
Oh!
[music becomes unsettling]
[eerie music playing]
Trish?
Josh?
-[gasps]
-[gasps, coughs]
Trish!
Trish, come on!
[eerie music continues]
[grunting, breathing heavily]
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
I'm gonna check on the engine.
[music intensifies]
[screams]
Josh!
-Josh?
-Josh!
[gasps]
-Josh! Come on!
-Josh, come on! Come on.
-[Josh gasps]
-[Maddie] Josh!
[muffled screams]
-Josh!
-Josh?
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh my God.
-[Josh gasps]
-[Trish] Josh!
-[Maddie] Josh! Come on!
-Come on!
-Josh, come on! Come on!
-Come on! Come on!
Come here, come on!
Josh, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
[suspenseful music fades]
[distantly] Josh!
[echoing] Josh!
Oh my God!
Josh!
[foreboding music playing]
[Trish] Oh my God.
[gasps] What do we do?
Let's just try to get
to some dry land.
Dry land. Dry land.
-There, see those rocks?
-Yeah. Yep.
[Maddie]
Let's get to those rocks
-and then we'll find a way out.
-[Trish] Yeah.
-Okay.
-Slow and steady.
Let's don't alert,
whatever is down there.
[tense music playing]
-Slow and steady.
-Yeah.
[tense music continues]
It's working, it's working.
It's working.
[gasps]
[tense music continues]
-Go!
-Go, go, go!
Go!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-Come on.
-Go! Come on! [grunts]
-[grunts]
-Come on! Go! [grunts]
-Come on! [grunts]
-[rope creaking]
[screams] No!
[indistinct clamoring]
-[music fades]
-[rope creaking]
[ominous music sting]
-[pants]
[grunts, pants]
Oh my God. What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
She did.
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[Maddie] Ceto.
[suspenseful music playing]
-[screams]
-[hearing aid screeches]
-[Ceto calling]
Maddie. Maddie? Maddie!
[dramatic music swells]
-[Ceto clicks]
-Holy shit.
-Shit.
[ominous music playing]
-Hold on! Hold on!
-[screams]
Hold on! Hold on!
[Maddie breathing heavily]
[both panting heavily]
We have to jump off.
What?
Either way, we're going to get
washed off.
So we have to jump off
so we can get a head start.
Okay?
You want us to get
back in the water?
What other choice do we have?
Come here. Come here.
-It's okay.
-Okay.
On three.
-[Ceto calling]
-[suspenseful music playing]
Two.
-Three. [groans]
-[hearing aid screeching]
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
[suspenseful music continues]
[grunts] Oh no! Batteries.
[Maddie] Oh my God!
[suspenseful music continues]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Maddie] Go! Trish, swim!
Go, Trish, go!
Trish, swim!
Go!
[grunts]
[suspenseful music crescendos]
[grunts] God!
[breathing heavily, groaning]
Maddie, you didn't jump!
I couldn't!
[water gurgling]
Catch my bag!
[grunts]
[Maddie] Quick! Grab it Trish.
Hurry! Hurry, before it sinks!
Hurry!
[Trish] Okay.
I got it. I got it.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Okay.
The second that she surfaces,
Maddie, you jump.
Okay?
You jump.
I'm ready!
-[tense music playing]
-[raft creaking]
[breathes heavily]
[raft creaking]
-[raft deflates]
-[gasping]
[dramatic music playing]
Go now! Go, Maddie!
Come on, come on, come on! Now!
Go Maddie, come on!
[gasps]
[Trish] Don't look back.
Come on, Maddie. Come on!
Swim, swim, swim, come on!
Come on, Maddie! Go, go, go!
[dramatic music continues]
Maddie, come on, come on!
Come here to me!
Maddie! Come on, come on!
Come on, come on!
[dramatic music continues]
Come on!
[screams]
[gasping]
Oh! You're okay. You're okay.
-[pants]
-Holy--
Oh my God, Trish, your leg.
-Oh. [grunts]
-[Trish groans]
[grunting]
God! Ow!
-Okay, okay, okay.
-[groans]
Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on.
-[Trish grunts]
-Okay.
Here.
Yeah, try that.
-[grunts]
-God!
-[Maddie grunts]
-Fuck!
[Maddie grunts] Fuck.
-[ripping]
-[Maddie grunting]
Here, here.
-[grunts]
-[screams]
-[Maddie panting]
-[Trish gasping]
[groans]
Okay.
-Okay.
-Just do it fast.
-Just really quickly.
-Okay.
Okay.
-Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
-Okay. Okay.
Look at me.
One.
Two.
-Three! I'm so--
-[screams]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Ow! What, what?
-Maddie, Maddie, Maddie.
Your foot.
-Oh my God, ow!
-Let me see it.
-Ow!
It hurts like a bitch!
-Okay, stay still, stay still,
stay still, stay still.
[pants]
Come here.
[groans] Okay.
-[Trish] Stay still.
-[Maddie] Okay.
[breathes rapidly]
-[Trish grunts]
-[Maddie screams]
[breathes heavily]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music fades]
-[Trish] How the hell
did Ceto get in here?
-I don't know.
I don't know.
I mean, I don't think
that they would have just...
just dumped her in here.
-Wait, didn't you say
you saw a man
in her tank last night?
-Were you being serious?
-Yeah.
But I don't know
that she for sure did that.
-[birds chirping]
-You don't know that she didn't.
[unsettling music resumes]
-It just doesn't make any sense.
Orcas have never,
ever killed a human in the wild.
The only time they've
ever killed anybody
is when they have
been trapped in captivity.
[dramatic music playing]
Oh my God.
She thinks she's still trapped
in captivity.
-And now we're trapped
in here with her.
[Trish shudders]
Oh, Trish.
Someone will come.
[dramatic music fades]
[Maddie]
Ceto sank the damn jet ski.
Now, all I've got is this.
[chuckles]
Lunch.
And breakfast.
And, last night's dinner.
Hmm.
And probably tonight's dinner.
-Better than nothing.
-[Trish] That's true.
Did you bring water or anything?
-No. And everything else I had
washed away back there.
Even my hearing aid batteries.
-Oh, shit.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, I dropped everything.
Your phone, your...
[gentle music playing]
-Oh my God.
-What?
Your stupid dad bag.
-What about my stupid dad bag?
-Your stupid dad bag.
Oh my God.
Oh, Maddie.
You beautiful dork. [chuckles]
This is good, this is good,
this is good.
Trish, I haven't seen you this
excited about a sandwich bag
since Mitchell Hope stole my
turkey club in the fifth grade.
-[laughs] You mean
that Mitchell Hopeless
after I kicked him in the dick?
And he cried
all the way to the sixth grade.
-[chuckles]
-He deserved it.
[gentle music continues]
[sighs]
We let this thing
swelter in the sun.
Eventually.
[chuckles]
We're gonna get water.
-Holy shit.
-Or sandwich bag sweat.
-Trish, you're a genius.
-[chuckles]
-Science.
-Oh my God.
How long is that going to take?
Four to six hours.
Give or take.
[gentle music fades]
-[screams] Hey!
-Somebody help!
-Somebody help us!
Please!
-Do you see anything? Huh?
-[pants]
Maddie.
Did you see anything? Huh?
-Nothing.
[somber music playing]
[waves lapping]
[inaudible chatter]
[somber music continues]
-[hearing aid screeching]
-[inaudible chatter]
[dramatic music playing]
Maddie. Maddie, look.
Maddie.
-Hey!
-Over here!
-Help us!
-Turn your boat over here!
-Over here!
-Help!
-Please!
-[Trish] Turn around!
-[Maddie] Please!
-Don't go!
-Here!
Come back! Come back! Over here!
Come back!
[Maddie] Help us!
Please!
Come back!
Please.
-[dramatic music fades]
-[Ceto calling]
-Why is she doing this to us?
-I don't know.
I can't say I blame her, though.
We've been trapped
in here a day.
She's been trapped in
a fish tank for nearly 20 years.
It's no wonder she hates humans.
To her in here...
we're no different.
-What are you saying?
-I'm just saying
that I empathize.
That's all.
-[hearing aid screeching]
-[dramatic music fades]
Oh my God.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-Oh my God.
[Ceto calls]
[dramatic music playing]
Oh my God.
Okay. I'm gonna get it.
Okay.
[grunts]
[dramatic music continues]
-Maddie.
-I'm okay, I'm okay.
-[grunts]
-[retches]
[dramatic music continues]
[Maddie breathes heavily] Okay.
Yeah.
[grunts, pants]
I got it.
-[Maddie] Anybody!
-[Trish] Help us!
[Maddie] Help!
[somber music playing]
-[Trish sobbing]
No one is coming.
-[Maddie] Trish.
-[Trish] No one is coming.
[Trish sobbing, shivering]
[Trish sniffles]
[somber music continues]
-Maddie.
Maddie.
-Hey.
What's wrong?
-I need to talk to you.
I need to tell you something.
-[Maddie] Oh my God.
It worked.
[groans]
[music becomes gentle]
[Trish groans]
Sandwich bag sweat.
[laughs]
Here.
[gentle music continues]
[gentle music fades]
What were you gonna say?
-I, uh...
Maddie,
why did you stop playing?
-Ever since Chad, um...
[pensive music playing]
I don't know.
-You know it's never too late,
right?
Maybe you could
go back to school.
-Yeah.
-[Trish] Yeah.
-Maybe.
We could graduate together
like we always said we would.
-[Maddie] I'm gonna be, um...
Like a dorky undergrad student,
so...
I doubt you'd really want to
hang out with me much anyway,
-you know?
-[Trish scoffs]
-True.
-[Maddie laughs]
Then again, you didn't
really mind hanging out
with the kid from
the wrong side of the tracks,
for all those years.
I felt like such a freak.
But you made me feel so normal.
[pensive music continues]
I always thought I could pay
you back one day, you know?
Take you someplace nice.
Once I'd paid off all my...
placement debt. [laughs]
And here we are.
[pensive music continues]
[sniffles]
-Trish, we have been there for
each other since we were kids.
You were always there
for me, too.
And we're gonna be there
for each other now,
and we are going
to get through this.
We're gonna get
through this, okay?
-Yeah.
-Ow.
[sighs heavily]
-[pensive music fades]
-[groans]
Wait, Trish,
did you say that you...
you paid off
your placement debt?
Oh my God, that's amazing.
How?
-Socials.
Goldmine.
-I am so proud of you.
-Yeah.
[laughs] Man, I don't know
about you, but I am...
starving.
You think we could try and
catch a fish with this thing?
-I have a better idea.
Revenge.
Maybe whatever I stepped
on yesterday is edible.
-Yeah, that's a good idea.
[uneasy music playing]
[thudding]
[uneasy music continues]
[uneasy music fades]
[Ceto clicking]
[dramatic music playing]
Maddie.
[Trish muffled] Maddie!
Maddie! [breathing heavily]
Come on, come on, come on!
[muffled] Come back.
[dramatic music continues]
-Come on!
-[music intensifies]
-[Trish] Come on! [grunts]
-[grunts]
Are you okay? Are you okay?
-[pants]
Oh my God.
[music fades]
[laughs]
[grunts]
Ah!
-[Maddie] Here.
-Maddie. Don't.
-[somber music playing]
That's Chad's
cremation stone box
[grunts]
-Maybe this can help.
It's okay.
[somber music continues]
[grunts]
[laughs]
May your beer always be cold.
-May your boys always be hot.
-Come hell or high water.
-It is you and me.
No matter what.
-No matter what.
[somber music continues]
Cheers.
[slurps]
[retches]
[music fades]
[slurps]
[groans]
[somber music resumes]
[somber music continues]
Maybe it's time.
Maybe it's the only time.
[Maddie] I love you so much.
Thank you for loving me.
I miss you.
I miss you a lot.
[somber music continues]
I love you so much.
I wish I could've
said that to you.
[somber music continues]
[somber music fades]
[sighs heavily]
-He loved you more
than anything, Maddie.
[sniffles]
-Yeah. [laughs]
-I'll never stop
thinking about that night.
I never should have
brought you here.
-Don't say that.
Couldn't have known.
-I was trying to make things...
better.
But I only made them worse.
-[Maddie] Hey.
Trish, it's not your fault.
Listen to me.
Trish you're my best friend,
and I'm telling you...
There's no way
that you could have known.
And there's...
there's no one else that
I'd rather be stuck on this,
shitty, shitty rock with.
[chuckles]
-I'm not your best friend.
[dramatic music playing]
A best friend wouldn't do
what I've done to you.
-Trish what are you
talking about?
-I needed money
for my placement at Brown.
You were never
supposed to be there,
you were supposed
to be at home studying.
-[Maddie]
She wasn't mad that I took
the last-minute shift
here instead?
-No, I covered for you.
Said you're at home
practicing your cello.
-[Trish] The guy was
someone I used to work with and
we were gonna go half.
-[phone line trilling]
-[dramatic music continues]
He left me a voicemail,
but it was too late.
He was never meant
to bring a gun!
[gunshot fires]
[dramatic music intensifies]
So I left.
I left you.
[cries]
[sobbing, sniffles]
You have to know
that every day when I wake up,
every night when I go to sleep,
all I can...
all I can think about is how
I wish I could go back in time
and pick up that call.
Maddie, you have to believe me.
You have to believe me.
[somber music playing]
[distantly] Maddie.
I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry
for everything that you've lost.
-No, don't! Don't say lost.
I did not lose anything.
You stole it from me.
-Why do you think
I couldn't be there for you
when you needed me most?
You know, I couldn't,
I... I couldn't look at you.
I couldn't... I couldn't face
what I did to you.
Okay, and now you've lost
the love of your life.
You've lost... You've lost
music, you've lost your
hearing--
-Don't touch me!
You don't get to sit here
and comfort me.
and say sorry.
-[Trish] I know, I know.
I'm so sorry I did that to you.
-You deserve
every single second of guilt.
-I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
-Good.
-[Trish] I'm so sorry.
[somber music continues]
[sobs]
Maddie.
-[sobbing]
-Maddie.
[somber music continues]
[Maddie crying]
[music becomes dramatic]
[thud]
[gasps]
-[Trish whispers] Maddie?
-[music fades]
Maddie, are you okay?
Maddie.
Maddie, we're not
gonna last much longer
if we stay on this rock.
We have to get off.
Our best bet at survival
is the perimeter.
[breathes heavily]
I'll swim to the sand...
the furthest point.
You swim to that rock,
it's the closest.
From there, you have the best
chance of making the perimeter.
You know, maybe she'll...
she'll be too confused
to chase either of us.
Or maybe not.
Okay.
All right, I'm gonna do it.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music continues]
-[panicked breathing]
-[music becomes ominous]
[ominous music continues]
[music becomes dramatic]
-Trish! Tr... Trish!
Trish?
What the hell are you doing?
-Making it right.
-No! No, Trish,
you don't have to do that!
No, Trish, it's okay!
It's okay, come back!
Come on, swim back!
-It's okay, you can swim back!
-[Ceto clicking]
Trish!
[dramatic music intensifies]
[Maddie]
Please, Trish! Swim! Go!
Swim! Go!
Trish! Go!
[gasps]
[dramatic music continues]
[music swells]
[gasps]
[dramatic music continues]
-[pants]
-[music fades]
[pants heavily]
[laughs]
[breathing heavily]
[airplane engine revving]
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh my God. Hey, help!
-Stop!
-Hey!
-[suspenseful music continues]
-[Maddie] Help us!
Hey!
Down here! Hey!
-Stop!
Turn around!
-Please come back, please!
[Trish] Stop it! Turn around!
-Stop the plane! Not again!
-[Ceto clicking]
-[Trish] Stop it please!
-[Maddie] Oh my God.
-[Trish] Stop!
-Come back!
-Oh my God, Trish!
-Stop the plane.
-Please get out
-of the water, Trish!
-[Trish] Come back!
-Stop the plane!
-Get out of the fucking water!
-[screams]
-[Maddie] No Trish, no!
Stop the fucking plane!
[ominous music playing]
[screams]
[grunts]
[ominous music continues]
[breathing heavily]
Oh my God, please.
[gasps, sighs]
[ominous music continues]
-[gasps]
-[Trish coughs, wheezes]
[grunts]
[coughs]
-[pants]
-[ominous music continues]
[ominous music continues]
[sobs] Oh my God, Trish.
Trish please, no!
Trish, no, please!
No, Trish!
[sobs]
[cries]
Please don't leave me!
[sobbing]
Please don't leave me, Trish!
Please don't leave me here.
[music fades]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[hearing aid beeps]
[hearing aid beeps]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[waves lapping]
[hearing aid beeps]
[muffled rustling]
[muffled white noise]
[white noise continues]
[dull thuds]
[thunder rumbling distantly]
-[lightening claps]
-[rain pattering]
[somber music playing]
[laughs]
[thunder rumbling]
[Ceto breaches]
[gasping]
[somber music continues]
You're trapped too.
[Ceto calls]
[Ceto spouts]
[somber music continues]
At least you tried to fight.
[music becomes suspenseful]
Okay.
[exhales]
[exhaling heavily]
[suspenseful music continues]
[music intensifies]
-[grunts]
-[music fades]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[breathes heavily]
[somber music playing]
[grunts softly]
[somber music continues]
[sobs]
[sniffles]
[grunts]
[somber music continues]
It's you and me.
No matter what.
[sobs]
[music becomes dramatic]
[grunts]
[somber music continues]
[Maddie]
Is that thing waterproof?
- What do you think?
[somber music playing]
[Trish] Maddie.
We're fighters. Right?
We always have been.
What other choice did we have?
[music becomes dramatic]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[inhales]
[dramatic music continues]
[dramatic music ends]
[ominous music playing]
[gasping]
Trish.
Okay.
Come on, come on, come on.
[cellphone trilling]
-No, no, no.
-[line disconnects]
No, no, no. Come on. [grunts]
[gasps]
[unsettling music playing]
[Ceto clicks]
-[breathing heavily]
-[Ceto calling]
[gasps]
[music becomes suspenseful]
[grunts, inhales]
[suspenseful music continues]
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[Ceto calls]
[suspenseful music resumes]
[Ceto calling]
[suspenseful music continues]
-[suspenseful music continues]
-[screaming]
[gurgled scream]
-[flesh squelches]
-[Ceto yelps]
[Ceto cries]
[Ceto calling]
[music becomes ominous]
[gasps]
-[Ceto calling]
-[soft music playing]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[coughs]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[poignant music playing]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[poignant music continues]
[poignant music continues
[music fades]
[audience applauding]
[Ceto calling]
[end theme music playing]